beyonceonline.com 2014-03-26

# Beyoncé

###  Beyonce.com Privacy Policy 

##  This Privacy Policy was last revised and is effective as of December 10th, 2013. 

THIS IS THE BEYONCE.COM OFFICIAL PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH IS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND FORMS A PART OF YOUR LEGAL AGREEMENT WITH US. PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY SINCE IT DESCRIBES THE TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION, THE CIRCUMSTANCES IN WHICH WE DISCLOSE OR SHARE INFORMATION AND HOW YOU CAN ACCESS, UPDATE OR DELETE CERTAIN INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED ABOUT YOU. 

####  What Information Do We Collect? 

We and any third party we engage for the purpose of administering, operating, hosting, configuring, designing, maintaining and providing internal support for our Website and Content (collectively, the “operational service providers”) collect certain non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit our Website (see Do you use cookies? below). We only collect Personal Information (defined below) from you when you submit it to us or provide it to us, such as when you email us or when you make a purchase on shop.beyonce.com.We use the term “Personal Information” to refer to any information you provide in connection with your use of our Website by which you can be personally identified. When you use our Website, we may collect your name, street address, telephone number, e-mail address, and billing information.   
Unless you voluntarily provide or send us Personal Information, we will always ask you to submit or provide it to us before collecting your Personal Information. If you provide or submit your Personal Information to us we will provide you with the ability to review, update and/or delete your Personal Information, subject to our obligations to comply with legal, regulatory, internal audit and record-keeping requirements. To update and/or delete your Personal Information you have on file with us, please send an email at info@parkwood-ent.com. 

####  How Do We Use Your Information? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to: 

  * Respond to your request and/or to complete your purchase;
  * Improve our Website (we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you);
  * Improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);
  * Improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);
  * Improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);

#####  Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future email communications, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

####  How Do We Protect Your Information? 

We maintain commercially reasonable standards of security and confidentiality. We also try to limit information access to individuals who need to have such access to perform their responsibilities associated with our Website and the Content on our Website. However, the Internet and communications cannot be guaranteed to be secure and it is possible that others may unlawfully intercept or access information, transmissions or communications to, from or within our Website. 

####  Do We Use Cookies? 

When you access our Website, we and our operational service providers and others who host our Website often use technology that can recognize, collect and/or transmit information that is associated with you, but which do not personally identify you. Although the term “cookie” specifically refers to a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes, we will use the term “cookie” to refer generically to any technology that can recognize, collect and/or transmit information about your visits to our Website. This type of information includes such data as the Internet or web domain that referred you, the type of operating system and browser you are using, the date and time of your visit, data relating to activities on our Website (e.g., so-called ‘clickstream’ data) and other technological attributes about your visit to our Website. This information is used to analyze trends, administer our Website, track user movements on our Websites, and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so we can continually improve our Website.   
Cookies also allow our Website to recognize your computer or access device each time you visit and cookies can keep count of how often you return. Cookies can also track how you use our Website and your preferences for features and functions, and cookies can store information such as your user name and password so that you don’t have to re-enter them each time you return to visit. Cookies don’t personally identify you or any particular user or individual.   
You can disable or turn the cookie feature off by changing the settings on your Internet browser and you can also change the settings to stop your browser from automatically accepting cookies. Although changing these settings may not affect your ability to browse, it may affect your ability to use certain features and functions of our Website and it may also require you to re-enter certain information each time you visit or attempt to use our Website. You should consult the operating instructions that apply to your browser to determine how to best configure your browser settings for your needs. 

####  Do We Disclose Any Information to Third Parties? 

We do not sell, rent, lease, provide or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated entities. We will always let you know if we intend to provide any of your Personal Information to an unaffiliated third party (e.g., not operational service providers) and we will ask you to consent (“opt-in”) whenever we intend to do so.   
We always have the right to disclose your Personal Information to our operational service providers. Our policy is to request that our operational service providers protect your privacy and not disclose your Personal Information to third party marketers that are not associated with our Website, nor are they permitted to use your Personal Information for their own marketing or promotional purposes. 

####  We also reserve the right to make your Personal Information available: 

  * When we are compelled by a governmental agency, law, regulation, a court or other legal process;
  * If we believe you are, have or may violate any law, regulation, our Terms and Conditions;
  * If we believe you are or may be a threat to safety, property, interests or rights of us or others;
  * In order to investigate, respond to or resolve problems or inquiries or defend our interests; and/or
  * In a merger, acquisition, change of control, joint venture or other business combination.

We reserve the right to disclose your non-personally identifiable visitor information to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

####  Third Party Links 

Our Website may contain or display information from advertisers, operational service providers or other third parties that offer to make information, goods or services available, provide opportunities to participate in promotions or engage in activities or that link or redirect your browser to other websites, materials or organizations. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on our Website, as well as for distributing our online, email, messages or web-based newsletters and other information. Third parties often also employ cookies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that even if you encounter an advertisement, link or reference to a Third Party Website on our Website and even if we have a relationship with them, we do not control them, their websites or their policies and practices regarding use of their websites, transaction policies or any rules they have regarding the use of cookies or collection, use or disclosure of your information (including Personal Information). These are within their control and not ours and the terms and conditions, as well as the privacy policies that apply to these third parties and their websites are their responsibility. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of Third Party Websites. 

####  Children’s Privacy and Parental Controls 

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 If you are under 18, you are not authorized to use our Website without express permission from your parent or legal guardian. Parents and legal guardians should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.   
Online Privacy Policy Only   
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline. 

####  Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions page, establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website. 

####  Your California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, allows individuals who are California residents that have provided their personal information to us to request certain information about our disclosures of certain categories of Personal Information (if any) to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding year. We do not currently share any Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. 

####  Changes to Our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes (if you have provided us with your email), and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date listed at the opt of this page. 

####  Operation of the Website - Disclaimer 

We endeavor to maintain this Website and its operation, but are not, and cannot be, responsible for the results of any defects that may exist in the Website or its operation. As to the operation of the Website, we expressly disclaim all warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to all implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement. We make no warranty that (i) the operation of the Website will meet your requirements; (ii) access to the Website will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, free of viruses, worms, trojan horses or other harmful components, or free of defects or errors; (iii) the results that may be obtained from the use of the Website will be accurate or reliable; or (iv) defects will be corrected. You assume the entire cost of all servicing, repair, or correction that may be necessary for your computer equipment and software as a result of any viruses, errors or any other problems whatsoever you may have as a result of visiting this Website. 

####  Indemnification 

You shall defend us against any demands, claims or actions brought against us or arising as a result of any breach or violation of these Terms and Conditions by you (each, a “Claim”) and you shall indemnify and hold us harmless from and against any and all losses, damages, costs and expenses (including attorneys' fees) resulting from any such Claim. We have the right, at our expense, to assume exclusive defense against any Claim and all negotiations for settlement and you agree to cooperate with us in the defense of any such Claim, at our request. 

####  Choice of Law 

These Terms and Conditions shall be construed and enforced under the laws of the State of New York applicable to parties resident in and contracts made, executed and wholly performed within the State of New York. You specifically agree and submit to the jurisdiction of the State and Federal Courts situated in the State, City and County of New York and you will not object to jurisdiction or venue on the grounds of lack of personal jurisdiction, inconvenient forum or otherwise. The Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act does not apply to our Terms and Conditions. You agree that you will not file or participate in a class action against us. IN ANY ACTION OR PROCEEDING COMMENCED TO ENFORCE ANY RIGHT OR OBLIGATION UNDER THIS AGREEMENT, YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR WITH RESPECT TO THE SUBJECT MATTER HEREOF, YOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY RIGHT YOU MAY NOW HAVE OR HEREAFTER POSSESS TO A TRIAL BY JURY. 

####  General Provisions 

These Terms and Conditions, together with our Privacy Policy, contain the entire agreement you have with us regarding our Website, Content and other subject matter set forth herein and supersedes any and all prior or inconsistent understandings that may apply to the subject matter.   
If, for any reason, we believe, have reason to believe, suspect or are notified of any act, omission or circumstances which may or could compromise or endanger the health, well being or safety of any person, cause or lead to damage to persons or property (tangible or intangible), adversely affects, infringes upon or misappropriates the rights of others, harasses or interferes with any other user or person, firm or enterprise, interferes with or bypasses our security or other protective measures applicable to our systems, networks and communications capabilities, breaches or violates our Terms or violates any law or regulation, we have the right, reserving cumulatively all other rights and remedies available to us at law, in equity and under this agreement with you, to report and provide information to any and all regulatory and law enforcement authorities and agencies and take any action permitted by law.   
Our Terms can only be modified by us as described above or by mutual written agreement, signed by an authorized representative of ours. The illegality, invalidity or unenforceability of any term or condition is severable and shall not affect the rest of our Terms and any unenforceable portion shall be construed in accordance with applicable law to the greatest extent possible. Headings are purely for reference and shall not affect the meaning of any term or condition. Any provision which must survive to allow us to enforce its meaning shall survive termination; however, no claim or action relating in any way to our Terms with respect to their subject matter, regardless of form or the basis of the claim, may be brought by you more than one (1) year after the cause of action has arisen (or if multiple causes, from the date the first such cause of action arose). 

####  Contact Us 

If you have any questions about our Terms, please contact us at: info@parkwood-ent.com.
